<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Billing, Payment and Accounts on Storj Docs</title><link>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/pricing/</link><description>Recent content in Billing, Payment and Accounts on Storj Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/pricing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Billing is Calculated</title><link>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/pricing/billing-and-payment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/pricing/billing-and-payment/</guid><description>How Billing is Calculated # Billing is aggregated at the project level. A project is the Storj DCS service construct used for aggregating usage, calculating billing, invoicing fees, and collecting payment. Projects are created by a single user, then multiple users may be added to a project team, and one user may be on more than one project. Within a project, usage is tracked at the bucket level and aggregated for invoicing to the project.</description></item><item><title>Free Plan</title><link>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/pricing/free-tier/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/pricing/free-tier/</guid><description>Free Plan # Storj DCS currently offers a free level of service to new accounts. When a customer creates a new account, the user automatically is able to use the Storj DCS service at no cost up to specified limits of service. The free level of service is limited to the level of service for a single project as described below:
150GB per month of static object storage for a single project.</description></item><item><title>Usage Limit Increases</title><link>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/pricing/usage-limit-increases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/pricing/usage-limit-increases/</guid><description>Usage Limit Increases # If the default Project Limits do not appear to be appropriate for your use case, you may request a Project Limit Increase form. Increases in Project Limits may result in increased costs associated with your usage of Storj DCS.
Free Plan # The Free Tier is not eligible for Project Limit Increases.
Object Storage # When you request an increase to the Object Storage Project Limit, there is no additional fee beyond the cost for any incremental Object Storage utilized on Storj DCS.</description></item></channel></rss>