<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on Storj Docs</title><link>/dcs/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on Storj Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/dcs/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Quickstart Guide</title><link>/dcs/getting-started/quickstart-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/getting-started/quickstart-guide/</guid><description>Quickstart Guide # Suggested Options # Rclone via Gateway MT - Interact with our S3 Hosted Gateway via Rclone. This is ideal for large files and industry compatibility.
Rclone with Hosted Gateway AWS CLI via Gateway MT - Interact with our S3 hosted gateway using the official AWS CLI. Ideal for high-performance uploads and large files.
Quickstart - AWS CLI and Hosted Gateway MT Alternative Options # Web Object Browser - Allows for uploading and managing files directly through the browser with no command-line tool required.</description></item><item><title>Quickstart - Object Browser</title><link>/dcs/getting-started/quickstart-objectbrowser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/getting-started/quickstart-objectbrowser/</guid><description>Quickstart - Object Browser # Introduction # The Storj DCS Satellite Admin Console supports uploading and managing objects directly through the browser with no command-line tool required. This component uses our hosted S3-compatible Gateway service.
By using hosted Gateway MT you are opting in to server-side encryption. Configure Object Browser Access # Navigate to the Buckets page within your project. If you do not have any buckets yet - we will create a demo-bucket for you.</description></item><item><title>Quickstart - AWS SDK and Hosted Gateway MT</title><link>/dcs/getting-started/quickstart-aws-sdk-and-hosted-gateway-mt/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/getting-started/quickstart-aws-sdk-and-hosted-gateway-mt/</guid><description>Quickstart - AWS SDK and Hosted Gateway MT # Storj now offers a hosted multitenant gateway (Gateway MT) that is backward compatible with S3. This means you’ll be able to integrate with the Storj network via HTTP, and you won’t have to run anything extra on your end.
By using hosted Gateway MT you are opting-in to server-side encryption. Using Gateway MT with AWS SDK is a 2-step process:</description></item></channel></rss>