<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Storj-hosted S3 Compatible Gateway on Storj Docs</title><link>/dcs/api-reference/s3-compatible-gateway/</link><description>Recent content in Storj-hosted S3 Compatible Gateway on Storj Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/dcs/api-reference/s3-compatible-gateway/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Using presigned URLs</title><link>/dcs/api-reference/s3-compatible-gateway/using-presigned-urls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/api-reference/s3-compatible-gateway/using-presigned-urls/</guid><description>Using presigned URLs # Introduction # All objects and paths are private and encrypted by default. However, it is possible to use a pre-signed URL via our S3-compatible gateway to enable unauthenticated customers/users to upload objects to buckets or access objects in buckets without providing an Access Grant or S3-compatible gateway access credentials.
HTTP GET vs Storj Linkshare Service # While we support this behavior via the S3-compatible pre-signed URL function, as an alternative to sharing with a customer/user via a GET, consider utilizing our Linkshare service.</description></item><item><title>Supported S3 Commands</title><link>/dcs/api-reference/s3-compatible-gateway/supported-s3-commands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/api-reference/s3-compatible-gateway/supported-s3-commands/</guid><description>Supported S3 Commands # The Storj DCS S3-compatible Gateway supports a RESTful API that is compatible with the basic data access model of the Amazon S3 API.
The Storj DCS S3 Gateway is well suited for many application architectures, but since the S3 standard was designed for centralized storage, there are a few areas where a decentralized architecture requires a different approach:
API Features Status (support/not supported) Remarks List Buckets Supported ListObjects Supported Object listing does not return a traditionally sorted list because keys are stored encrypted.</description></item></channel></rss>