<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Quickstart - Satellite Admin Console on Storj Docs</title><link>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/</link><description>Recent content in Quickstart - Satellite Admin Console on Storj Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Creating Your Account</title><link>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/creating-your-account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/creating-your-account/</guid><description>Creating Your Account # The first step in creating your developer account on Storj DCS is to select a Satellite. A Satellite is a set of hosted services that is responsible for a range of functions on the network, including the node discovery system, node address information caching, per-object metadata storage, storage node reputation management, billing data aggregation, storage node payment, data audit and repair, as well as user account and authorization management.</description></item><item><title>Manage Projects</title><link>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/manage-projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/manage-projects/</guid><description>Manage Projects # When you log into the Satellite Admin Console, you start on the Project Dashboard for your default Project. A Project is the basic unit for aggregating usage, calculating billing, invoicing fees, collecting payment, and handling access management. Users can create multiple Projects and projects are invoiced separately. Within a Project, usage is tracked at the Bucket level and aggregated for invoicing to the Project. Project names are not client-side encrypted so that they may be rendered in the Satellite user interface.</description></item><item><title>Dashboard</title><link>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/dashboard/</guid><description>Dashboard # When you log into the Satellite Admin Console, you start on the Project Dashboard for your default Project. A Project is the basic unit for aggregating usage, calculating billing, invoicing fees, collecting payment, and handling access management. Users can create multiple Projects and projects are invoiced separately. Within a Project, usage is tracked at the Bucket level and aggregated for invoicing to the Project. Project names are not client-side encrypted so that they may be rendered in the Satellite user interface.</description></item><item><title>Buckets</title><link>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/objects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/objects/</guid><description>Buckets # The Object Browser is a web interface for creating/deleting buckets, uploading, downloading, viewing the object map, and sharing access to objects stored in a Project on Storj DCS.
This is such a popular feature, it has its very own Quickstart Guide for the Object Browser. In the Quickstart Guide for the Object Browser, you&amp;rsquo;ll learn:
Setting your encryption passphrase How to create and delete Buckets How to upload objects to Buckets, download and delete them.</description></item><item><title>Access</title><link>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/access-grants/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/access-grants/</guid><description>Access # An Access Grant is a security envelope that contains a satellite address, a restricted API Key, and a restricted path-based encryption key - everything an application needs to locate an object on the network, access that object, and decrypt it.
Learn more about Access Management and Access Grants or check out the FAQ on Access Grants and Encryption Keys. The Access Grant screen allows you to create or delete Access Grants, and generate credentials for the Storj DCS S3-compatible Gateway from an Access Grant.</description></item><item><title>Users</title><link>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/users/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/users/</guid><description>Users # If you need to collaborate with other developers on a project, you can add other developers who have an account on the same Satellite as your project.
When you add another user to your project, that user will have full access to the Project Dashboard, Object Browser, and access Grants for your Project. Navigate to the Users screen.
Select the Add button
Type in the email addresses that the users have registered with their Satellite Accounts.</description></item><item><title>Billing</title><link>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/billing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/billing/</guid><description>Billing # Introduction # The Billing screen allows you to see all your projects and their estimated charges for the Current Billing Period, the Invoices for a Previous Billing Period and Billing History. You can also see an Available Balance, Balance History and Free Credits. At the bottom you can see and add Coupons.
View a Previous Billing Period and Invoices # If you select the Current Billing Period on top right, you will see two additional options:</description></item><item><title>Resources</title><link>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/resources/</guid><description>Resources # Here you can select:
Docs Forum Support</description></item><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/quick-start/</guid><description>Quick Start # These Quick Start Wizards can help you to use the Satellite Admin Console.</description></item><item><title>My Account</title><link>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/my-account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/getting-started/satellite-developer-account/my-account/</guid><description>My Account # Introduction # The My Account will allow you to read documentation about the Satellite, change your Account Settings or Logout from the Satellite Admin Console.
If you click the (i) icon on the right of the Satellite short name, you will be redirected to the Key Architectural Construct Satellite.
Account Settings # The Account Settings page allows you to Edit Profile, Change Password or enable/disable Two-Factor Authentication.</description></item></channel></rss>