<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Before You Begin on Storj Docs</title><link>/node/before-you-begin/</link><description>Recent content in Before You Begin on Storj Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/node/before-you-begin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Signup for Auth Token</title><link>/node/before-you-begin/signup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/before-you-begin/signup/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Authorization Token</title><link>/node/before-you-begin/auth-token/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/before-you-begin/auth-token/</guid><description>Authorization Token # Authorization Token # Make sure you have copied your personal single-use authorization token from the Node Hosting signup page. It looks like this:
If you do not have an authorization token yet, sign up to Hosting a node. By using your authorization token, you agree to the Storage Node Operator Terms and Conditions.</description></item><item><title>Prerequisites</title><link>/node/before-you-begin/prerequisites/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/before-you-begin/prerequisites/</guid><description>Prerequisites # Hardware Requirements (Recommended) # ✅ One (1) processor core dedicated to each node service
✅ 8 TB and a maximum of 24 TB of available space per node
Minimum of 550 GB with no maximum of available space per node
✅ 16+ TB of unmetered bandwidth available per month; unlimited preferred
Minimum of 2 TB of bandwidth available per month
✅ 100 Mbps bandwidth upstream
Minimum of 5 Mbps bandwidth upstream</description></item><item><title>Important Security Consideration</title><link>/node/before-you-begin/important-security-consideration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/before-you-begin/important-security-consideration/</guid><description>Important Security Consideration # Do not connect your computer directly to the internet without the assistance of a firewall. # Make sure you&amp;rsquo;re connected to the Internet through a router and not through a modem without a firewall. Our software serves requests from the Internet, but not all software you may have installed is designed to be exposed to the Internet directly. This is especially true for users on Windows with applications responding to requests on all IPs.</description></item></channel></rss>