<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CLI Install on Storj Docs</title><link>/node/setup/cli/</link><description>Recent content in CLI Install on Storj Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/node/setup/cli/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Docker</title><link>/node/setup/cli/docker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/setup/cli/docker/</guid><description>Docker # Install Docker # To setup a Storage Node, you first must have Docker installed. Install Docker by following the appropriate installation guide for your OS.
Windows Windows Docker Installation
Please, install version 2.1.0.5 if your Windows doesn&amp;rsquo;t support WSL2: https://docs.docker.com/docker-for-windows/release-notes/#docker-desktop-community-2105
All newer versions for Hyper-V have various issues, such as losing network connection as described in this thread: https://forum.storj.io/t/latest-docker-desktop-for-windows-compatibility/6045
Docker Toolbox is not supported Linux Ubuntu Docker Installation</description></item><item><title>Storage Node</title><link>/node/setup/cli/storage-node/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/setup/cli/storage-node/</guid><description>Storage Node # Download the Storage Node Docker Container # docker pull storjlabs/storagenode:latest Storage Node Concepts # Before running your Storage Node for the first time, please note the Storage Node concepts to be used.
Concepts Description -p How to specify ports - which are points through which information flows between your Node and the Storj network. -p &amp;lt;host-port&amp;gt;:&amp;lt;container-port&amp;gt;/tcp -p &amp;lt;host-port&amp;gt;:&amp;lt;container-port&amp;gt;/udp /tcpand/udpwill allow your node to connect with the network via both TCP and UDP</description></item><item><title>Software Updates</title><link>/node/setup/cli/software-updates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/setup/cli/software-updates/</guid><description>Software Updates # Automatic Updates # You can set up automatic updates for your storagenode Docker container using watchtower. Watchtower will look for new updates to the Docker container on Docker Hub in a random interval between 12 and 72 hours and automatically update your storage node when it sees a new version.
First, please pull the latest watchtower image from docker:
docker pull storjlabs/watchtower To set up auto-update for storagenode, please run the following command once:</description></item><item><title>Dashboard</title><link>/node/setup/cli/dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/setup/cli/dashboard/</guid><description>Dashboard # Storage Node Operator Web Dashboard # If you want to access this dashboard from a device on your local network, in your docker run command, use -p 14002:14002 instead of -p 127.0.0.1:14002:14002
If you want to access this dashboard remotely, use this guide: How to remote access the web dashboard
Open the following URL in your web browser:
Directly on your node: # http://127.0.0.1:14002/ Device on local network: # http://&amp;lt;your-nodes-local-ip&amp;gt;:14002/ Storage Node Dashboard Concepts # Concept Description Satellite Satellites act as the mediator between clients (people up- and downloading data) and Storage Node Operators (people storing data).</description></item></channel></rss>