<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Payment Methods on Storj Docs</title><link>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/storj-token/</link><description>Recent content in Payment Methods on Storj Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/storj-token/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Promotional Credits</title><link>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/storj-token/promotional-credits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/storj-token/promotional-credits/</guid><description>Promotional Credits # The Storj DCS Service includes incentive programs to encourage adoption and use of the platform. These incentives are operationalized as Promotional Credits and include Credits and Coupons.
Credits # Credits are a bonus amount that is deposited to a user’s account that the user receives when paying in STORJ token. Credits may be offered from time to time, at varying percentages, at our sole discretion. You will be notified at the time of your deposit if a Credit is offered.</description></item><item><title>Debits Against Payment Methods</title><link>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/storj-token/debits-against-payment-methods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/storj-token/debits-against-payment-methods/</guid><description>Debits Against Payment Methods # If you have an amount due, your payment methods will be debited in the following order (the order of operations is entirely programmatic):
Coupon - Any valid Coupon on an account will first be used to pay an invoice amount. If the entire invoice is paid with Coupons, no further debits are made in that billing cycle. If, after all Coupons are exhausted in a billing cycle, a balance on an invoice remains, the balance will be debited using the next available payment method; Credits - After applying any Coupons, any valid Credit on an account will then be used to pay an invoice amount.</description></item><item><title>Changing Payment Methods</title><link>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/storj-token/changing-payment-methods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/storj-token/changing-payment-methods/</guid><description>Changing Payment Methods # Users may change payment methods on accounts, but at least one valid payment method must be configured on an account at all times.
Changing Credit Cards # If you want to change the credit card on an account, follow the process outlined above to add a second card under Payment Methods, Add Card.
Once a second card has been added, you may select the new card as the Default card.</description></item><item><title>Deleting a Payment Method</title><link>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/storj-token/deleting-a-payment-method/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/storj-token/deleting-a-payment-method/</guid><description>Deleting a Payment Method # To use the Storj DCS Paid Tier, a user must have a valid payment method on their account. Users may delete payment methods:
when substituting for another valid payment method; or when requesting the deprovisioning of the account; or when requesting the deletion of an account The process for substituting valid payment methods is outlined above. Once a new payment method is added, the old payment method may be removed.</description></item><item><title>Expired Credit Card</title><link>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/storj-token/expired-credit-card/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/storj-token/expired-credit-card/</guid><description>Expired Credit Card # If the default credit card on an account expires, an email will be sent to the registered email address on the account notifying the owner of the account that the credit card has expired. If a secondary credit card has been added to the account, the secondary card will be charged for any usage fees, and service will not be interrupted. If a secondary card is not added and the user did not enable a STORJ payment method, a valid payment method must be added to the account.</description></item><item><title>Reporting a Payment Problem</title><link>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/storj-token/reporting-a-payment-problem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/storj-token/reporting-a-payment-problem/</guid><description>Reporting a Payment Problem # We use best-in-class partners for payment processing (Stripe for credit card payments and CoinPayments for STORJ utility token transactions). Still, sometimes unanticipated issues can arise.
If the issue is with a credit card payment, please start by submitting a support ticket through our Storj DCS support portal. We will attempt to resolve the issue prior to escalating with Stripe.
If the issue is with a STORJ token transaction, you should first contact CoinPayments to confirm that your STORJ token transaction was received by CoinPayments.</description></item></channel></rss>