<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Billing, Payment &amp; Accounts on Storj Docs</title><link>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/</link><description>Recent content in Billing, Payment &amp; Accounts on Storj Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Requesting a Refund</title><link>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/requesting-a-refund/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/requesting-a-refund/</guid><description>Requesting a Refund # We want all of our users to receive value when they choose the Storj DCS Platform for their storage needs. While we strive to provide world-class service it is possible that a customer may request a refund. Refunds will only be granted based on the circumstances set forth in the Terms of Use and Terms of Service. Coupons and Credits are not refundable under any circumstances.</description></item><item><title>Closing an Account</title><link>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/closing-an-account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/closing-an-account/</guid><description>Closing an Account # We want all of our users to receive value when they choose the Storj DCS Platform for their storage needs, but it’s possible that a user may no longer need Storj DCS services. If a user wants to stop using an account and permanently delete the account, the user may submit a request for this only after following the steps outlined below to eliminate platform usage.</description></item><item><title>Data Retention Policy</title><link>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/data-retention-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/billing-payment-and-accounts-1/data-retention-policy/</guid><description>Data Retention Policy # All unpaid balances must be paid via a valid payment method in a billing cycle. Note that if no valid payment method remains on an account, usage limits may be reduced to zero. If all credit cards expire or are invalid, or the STORJ token balance is exhausted and no new payment method is added on a project, after a reasonable time and opportunity to add a payment method, we reserve the right to reclaim the available resources (the storage space and bandwidth made available by Storage Node Operators to the Storj network) and delete the data from Storj DCS if a valid payment method is not added and any unpaid fees are not paid.</description></item></channel></rss>