<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Concepts on Storj Docs</title><link>/dcs/concepts/</link><description>Recent content in Concepts on Storj Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/dcs/concepts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Understanding Storj DCS</title><link>/dcs/concepts/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/concepts/overview/</guid><description>Understanding Storj DCS # Overview # Storj makes open-source software that anyone can run - individuals with a Network Attached Storage Device or NAS, those with desktop computers that are always on, businesses, or data centers - that allows these users to share unused disk drive space and bandwidth with the network. Our software aggregates all of that storage capacity and bandwidth to create an extremely secure, private, and durable cloud storage service for developers.</description></item><item><title>Definitions</title><link>/dcs/concepts/definitions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/concepts/definitions/</guid><description>Definitions # The Storj DCS service uses an array of different technologies such as strong encryption and erasure codes to ensure a differentiated level of privacy and security across a network of peer classes. Some of the terms we use may be familiar and some may be new, but if you see a word you don&amp;rsquo;t recognize or see a familiar word in a different context, you&amp;rsquo;ll probably find a useful definition here:</description></item><item><title>Key Architecture Constructs</title><link>/dcs/concepts/key-architecture-constructs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/concepts/key-architecture-constructs/</guid><description>Key Architecture Constructs # At a high level, object storage is a well-understood technology with established vendors and standards for integration. Storj DCS brings a number of new capabilities to make it easy for developers to build more secure and private applications and, as with any new and disruptive technology, the key to maximizing the potential value of that technology is understanding how that technology can be practically applied to solve real-world problems.</description></item><item><title>Connectors</title><link>/dcs/concepts/connectors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/concepts/connectors/</guid><description>Connectors # Building Storj DCS Connectors # Connectors bridge the gap between the applications we use every day and the underlying storage infrastructure on which application data is stored. Our team has worked with our partners to build a series of connectors between Storj DCS, our decentralized cloud storage service, and our partners’ applications.
What is a Storj DCS Connector # A Storj DCS connector is an application-level integration that enables the use of decentralized cloud storage in consumer software.</description></item><item><title>Data Structure</title><link>/dcs/concepts/data-structure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/concepts/data-structure/</guid><description>Data Structure # Hierarchy of Data Storage # Projects
Projects allow you to invite team members, manage billing, and manage access for various apps or users.
Buckets Buckets represent a collection of objects. You can upload, download, list, and delete objects of any size or shape.
Objects
Each object typically includes the data itself, a variable amount of metadata, and a globally unique identifier (Object key) which uniquely identifies the object in a bucket.</description></item><item><title>File Redundancy</title><link>/dcs/concepts/file-redundancy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/concepts/file-redundancy/</guid><description>File Redundancy # Durability and expansion factor # In a decentralized storage network, any storage node could go offline permanently at any time. A storage network’s redundancy strategy must store data in a way that provides access with high probability, even though any given number of individual nodes may be in an offline state. To achieve a specific level of durability (defined as the probability that data remains available in the face of failures), many products in this space (Filecoin, MaidSafe, Siacoin, GFS, Ceph, IPFS, etc.</description></item><item><title>Multiregion Availability</title><link>/dcs/concepts/multiregion-availability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/concepts/multiregion-availability/</guid><description>Multiregion Availability # Breaking the Storj DCS service into multiple peer classes on the network provides the maximum flexibility to network participants. While the majority of the network is operated by third parties, the components and architecture are all designed to be inherently multi-region to meet strict SLAs for availability and durability.
Storage Nodes # One key to the durability of the network is the distribution of data over a heterogeneous network of statistically uncorrelated nodes.</description></item><item><title>Usage Limits</title><link>/dcs/concepts/limits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/concepts/limits/</guid><description>Usage Limits # Usage Limits allow us to ensure a consistent level of service for all customers. We have limits for usage established per Project on all Storj DCS Satellites. All limits are set to default values as follows:
PRO Account (Paid Tier) # Credit Card Payment method # Adding a credit card as payment method will result in your per project limits being automatically raised to Pro Account limits:</description></item><item><title>Satellite (Metadata Region)</title><link>/dcs/concepts/satellite/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/concepts/satellite/</guid><description>Satellite (Metadata Region) # The Satellite is a set of hosted services that is responsible for a range of functions on the network, including the node discovery system, node address information caching, per-object metadata storage, storage node reputation management, billing data aggregation, storage node payment, data audit and repair, as well as user account and authorization management.
Users have accounts on and trust specific Satellites. Any user can run their own Satellite, but we expect many users will choose to avoid the operational complexity and create an account on another Satellite hosted by a trusted third party such as Storj Labs, a friend, group, or workplace.</description></item><item><title>S3 Compatibility</title><link>/dcs/concepts/s3-compatibility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/concepts/s3-compatibility/</guid><description>S3 Compatibility # The Storj DCS S3-compatible Gateway supports a RESTful API that is compatible with the basic data access model of the Amazon S3 API.
The Storj DCS S3 Gateway is well-suited for many application architectures, but the S3 standard was designed for centralized storage and there are a few areas where a decentralized architecture requires a different approach.
Storj DCS offers two options for S3 compatibility: GatewayMT, a hosted S3-compatible service and GatewayST, a self-hosted S3-compatible binary to run your own endpoint (see the compatibility table for GatewayST in our GitHub repo).</description></item><item><title>File Repair</title><link>/dcs/concepts/file-repair/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/concepts/file-repair/</guid><description>File Repair # All of the nodes on the network are operated by third party volunteers. One key to the durability of the network is the distribution of data over a heterogeneous network of statistically uncorrelated nodes. Since the storage nodes are operated by different people, in different regions, on different power supplies, with different internet connections, etc., the risk of failure is highly distributed. While the risk of failure for any individual node is very low, the risk of 51 out of 80 nodes failing simultaneously is astronomically low.</description></item></channel></rss>