<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Access Management on Storj Docs</title><link>/dcs/concepts/access/</link><description>Recent content in Access Management on Storj Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/dcs/concepts/access/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Access Revocation</title><link>/dcs/concepts/access/access-revocation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/concepts/access/access-revocation/</guid><description>Access Revocation # While delegated authorization and the ability to generate Access Grants at the edge provides the opportunity to create more private and secure applications, there are design considerations to take into account when building applications with data sharing capabilities based on long-lived bearer tokens.
While it is possible to create Access Grants with time-based restrictions and to required Access Grants be refreshed as they expire, applications must be able to revoke access to data.</description></item><item><title>Capability Based Access vs Access Control Lists</title><link>/dcs/concepts/access/capability-based-access-control/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/concepts/access/capability-based-access-control/</guid><description>Capability Based Access vs Access Control Lists # From a security-design standpoint, the capability model introduces a fundamentally better approach to identity and access management than Public Cloud’s ACL framework.
By tying access to keys, rather than a centralized control system, capability-based models push security to the edge, decentralizing the large ACL attack vector and creating a more secure IAM system.
The capability-based model solves both the ambient authority trap and the confused deputy problem by design.</description></item><item><title>Access Management at the Edge</title><link>/dcs/concepts/access/access-management-at-the-edge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/concepts/access/access-management-at-the-edge/</guid><description>Access Management at the Edge # One of the areas where we’re seeing the strongest interest from developers, customers and partners building apps is our security model and access control layer. The security and privacy capabilities of the platform are some of the most differentiating features and they give our partners and customers some exciting new tools.
Distributed and decentralized cloud storage is a fantastic way to take advantage of underutilized storage and bandwidth, but in order to provide highly available and durable cloud storage, we needed to build in some fairly sophisticated security and privacy controls.</description></item></channel></rss>