<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>FAQ's on Storj Docs</title><link>/node/resources/faq/</link><description>Recent content in FAQ's on Storj Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/node/resources/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How is the online score calculated?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/how-the-online-score-is-calculated/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/how-the-online-score-is-calculated/</guid><description>How is the online score calculated? # The implementation matches the design doc here: Storage Node Downtime Tracking with Audits.
In production, we have 12-hour windows and a 30-day tracking period, which translates to 60 windows per tracking period and two windows a day. Every single audit the storage node gets will affect its online score to some extent. For example, if a node got audited during 30 seconds of downtime, that offline audit will have a negative effect on the online_score of the storage node.</description></item><item><title>Where can I check for a new version?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/where-can-i-check-for-a-new-version/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/where-can-i-check-for-a-new-version/</guid><description>Where can I check for a new version? # We have a proposal for the Storage Nodes Operators - let&amp;rsquo;s work together and keep our network up to date to offer a great service to our Customers!
Please, read this thread on the forum: Keeping your node up to date, changes to storage node software! PLEASE READ this thread!
Automatic updater # The best way is to run the recommended Automatic updates (for Docker) - this is not necessary with the Windows GUI version as it already has an automatic updater included, and the Linux version with similar capabilities is coming soon.</description></item><item><title>How do I check my node when I'm away from my machine?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/check-my-node/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/check-my-node/</guid><description>How do I check my node when I&amp;rsquo;m away from my machine? # In a future update, we&amp;rsquo;ll have e-mail notifications for when your Node goes down. Until then, a great way to stay updated with your Node&amp;rsquo;s status is to use UptimeRobot.
UptimeRobot will check to see if your port is listening every x minutes. When your port is not listening, you will receive an e-mail alerting you that your port is closed, meaning there&amp;rsquo;s something going on with your Node.</description></item><item><title>What if my machine restarts or shuts down?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/machine-restart-shutdown/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/machine-restart-shutdown/</guid><description>What if my machine restarts or shuts down? # If you have properly mounted your hard drive (if on Linux, using static mount via /etc/fstab), then your Node should start up again automatically after your machine has rebooted.
However, power failures on machines not protected by a UPS or other abrupt disconnections may cause database corruption leading to errors such as: database error: database disk image is malformed or database: file is not a database in your logs).</description></item><item><title>How do I shutdown my node for system maintenance?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/system-maintenance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/system-maintenance/</guid><description>How do I shutdown my node for system maintenance? # If you need to shutdown the Storage Node for maintenance on your system, run:
CLI Install docker stop -t 300 storagenode GUI Windows Install Elevated PowerShell:
Stop-Service storagenode Or click the &amp;ldquo;Stop&amp;rdquo; button in the Windows Services applet on &amp;ldquo;Storj V3 Storage Node&amp;rdquo; service
After you finished your maintenance, restart the Node with:
CLI Install docker start storagenode GUI Windows Install Elevated PowerShell:</description></item><item><title>What other commands can I run?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/other-commands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/other-commands/</guid><description>What other commands can I run? # Run help to see other commands:
CLI Install docker exec -it storagenode /app/storagenode help GUI Windows Install PowerShell:
&amp;amp;&amp;#34;$env:ProgramFiles\Storj\Storage Node\storagenode.exe&amp;#34; --help Run the following to execute other commands:
CLI Install docker exec -it storagenode /app/storagenode &amp;lt;&amp;lt;command&amp;gt;&amp;gt; GUI Windows Install PowerShell:
&amp;amp;&amp;#34;$env:ProgramFiles\Storj\Storage Node\storagenode.exe&amp;#34; &amp;lt;&amp;lt;command&amp;gt;&amp;gt;</description></item><item><title>How do I check my logs?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/check-logs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/check-logs/</guid><description>How do I check my logs? # You can look at your logs to see if you have some errors indicating that something is not functioning properly:
CLI Install docker logs storagenode Use this command if you just want to see the last 20 lines of the log:
docker logs --tail 20 storagenode For CLI Docker install on Windows, if you have redirected your logs to a file, please execute the following command in PowerShell, inserting your actual path to your log file instead of &amp;ldquo;pathtologfile&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>How do I redirect my logs to a file?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/redirect-logs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/redirect-logs/</guid><description>How do I redirect my logs to a file? # 1. To redirect the logs to a file, stop your Node:
CLI Install docker stop -t 300 storagenode GUI WIndows Install Elevated PowerShell:
Stop-Service storagenode Or click the &amp;ldquo;Stop&amp;rdquo; button in the Windows Services applet on &amp;ldquo;Storj V3 Storage Node&amp;rdquo; service
2. Then edit your config.yaml (you can use nano or vi editor for Linux/MacOS or Notepad++ for Windows) to add (or change) the log location (see Where can I find a config.</description></item><item><title>How do I check my L2 zkSync payouts?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/how-do-i-check-my-l2-payouts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/how-do-i-check-my-l2-payouts/</guid><description>How do I check my L2 zkSync payouts? # If you opted-in for zkSync, you can check your payout in three ways:
Payout section on the Dashboard # You can click the View on zkScan button on the main page of your web-dashboard (see Dashboard for CLI and Dashboard for GUI), as shown in the screenshot of the dashboard Payout section below. This will send you to your zkSync wallet page where you can review the latest L2 payout transactions received.</description></item><item><title>How does held back amount work?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/held-back-amount/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/held-back-amount/</guid><description>How does held back amount work? # The held back amount (staked) component provides a preferred way for Node Operators to exit the network. This model optimizes liveliness by deterring Nodes to exit the network without transferring their pieces (thus limiting repair costs). Importantly, this strikes an equilibrium between a very low cost of entry for Nodes while also way to insulate against the cost of data repair.
Nodes don&amp;rsquo;t need to provide any up-front stake to start earning STORJ tokens as a Storage Node Operator.</description></item><item><title>How do I change values like wallet address or storage capacity?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/how-do-i-change-my-parameters-such-as-payout-address-allotted-storage-space-and-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/how-do-i-change-my-parameters-such-as-payout-address-allotted-storage-space-and-bandwidth/</guid><description>How do I change values like wallet address or storage capacity? # 1. Stop and remove the running Storage Node Docker container (CLI) or stop the service (GUI Windows):
CLI Install docker stop -t 300 storagenode docker rm storagenode GUI Windows Install Elevated PowerShell:
Stop-Service storagenode Or click the &amp;ldquo;Stop&amp;rdquo; button in the Windows Services applet on &amp;ldquo;Storj V3 Storage Node&amp;rdquo; service
2. Run your Storage Node again after editing needed parameters:</description></item><item><title>How do I setup static mount via /etc/fstab for Linux?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/linux-static-mount/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/linux-static-mount/</guid><description>How do I setup static mount via /etc/fstab for Linux? # First, run the following command and find the name of the hard drive you wish to use (for example sda2)
lsblk Once you find it, we will now get the Unique ID (UUID) of the hard drive
lsblk -d -fs /dev/&amp;lt;location (example: sda2)&amp;gt; Copy the UUID, as well as the FSTYPE. We’ll need that later.
Next, we will create a new directory in the /mnt folder where you want your Storj files to be stored; you can name this directory whatever you would like.</description></item><item><title>How do I estimate my potential earnings for a given amount of space and bandwidth?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/how-do-i-estimate-my-potential-earnings-for-given-amount-of-space-and-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/how-do-i-estimate-my-potential-earnings-for-given-amount-of-space-and-bandwidth/</guid><description>How do I estimate my potential earnings for a given amount of space and bandwidth? # We have a great Community Earnings Estimator to give you an idea how much time it may take to fill your provided free disk space and how much you may earn.
Please be aware - this is only an estimator, not a calculator. Unlike for mining cryptocurrencies, the estimated potential earnings are not guaranteed because the space and bandwidth are used by real people, not machines.</description></item><item><title>Why am I not storing more data?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/storing-more-data/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/storing-more-data/</guid><description>Why am I not storing more data? # The most important aspect to increase the amount of data stored on your Node (and thus maximizing payout) is to build reputation of your Node’s ID over an extended period of time**.**
When a Node first joins the network, there is a probationary period, during which the Node has to prove itself (e.g. maintaining a certain uptime and performance levels, passing all content audits).</description></item><item><title>Why is the network not using all of my storage and bandwidth?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/storage-bandwidth-usage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/storage-bandwidth-usage/</guid><description>Why is the network not using all of my storage and bandwidth? # The quick answer is, your Node&amp;rsquo;s reputation is still growing. The Node isn&amp;rsquo;t yet storing stripes of frequently accessed pieces. Luckily for Storage Node Operators, we’ve optimized the network to provide the maximum amount of bandwidth allocation based on the operation of a single node in a bandwidth-constrained environment.
This means that running a single Node per location (where one location = a discrete network with separate IP address and bandwidth/bandwidth cap) will yield the best results (highest reputation, most storage contracts from satellites and most earned STORJ tokens) for Storage Node Operators.</description></item><item><title>Why are my payouts so low?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/low-payouts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/low-payouts/</guid><description>Why are my payouts so low? # If you believe you should have gotten higher payouts, please run the earnings estimator and then compare each Satellite’s payouts to the amount you received in the transactions sent to your payout address for the month in question. Please wait to submit any support ticket until we have announced that all payouts have been completed for the month. Payouts are sent monthly, in the first two weeks after the month being paid is done.</description></item><item><title>How do I estimate my payouts per Satellite?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/estimate-payouts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/estimate-payouts/</guid><description>How do I estimate my payouts per Satellite? # If you would like to estimate how much you can expect to get paid for running your Node during a given month, please follow the instructions here.
This information is also available on the Web-dashboard (docker) or Web-dashboard for Windows/Linux GUI.
The script above can be used to check the estimations displayed on the dashboard and correctness of payout. If your node is working properly, the values for both sources should almost be the same.</description></item><item><title>What if I'm using a remote connection?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/remote-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/remote-connection/</guid><description>What if I&amp;rsquo;m using a remote connection? # If you must use a remote connection, due to the length of time it takes for some of the steps, it&amp;rsquo;s highly recommended to run them inside a virtual console like TMUX or SCREEN.
It is recommended to perform the next steps local to the machine, and not via a remote connection.</description></item><item><title>How to remote access the web dashboard</title><link>/node/resources/faq/how-to-remote-access-the-web-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/how-to-remote-access-the-web-dashboard/</guid><description>How to remote access the web dashboard # Enable the web dashboard for your setup # Windows See Dashboard for Windows GUI or Dashboard for docker versionLinux See Dashboard for docker versionmacOS See Dashboard for docker version Install a ssh server on your PC with the storagenode # Windows Get started with OpenSSHLinux sudo apt update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo apt install ssh -y macOS How to Enable SSH on a Mac from the Command Line Install a ssh client on your device # Windows Add-WindowsCapability -Online -Name OpenSSH.</description></item><item><title>What if I'm using the CLI Install on Windows / MacOS?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/cli-on-windows-mac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/cli-on-windows-mac/</guid><description>What if I&amp;rsquo;m using the CLI Install on Windows / MacOS? # Your Node may require extra monitoring. You may have to frequently restart Docker from the Docker desktop application when your Last Contact shown in the dashboard gets OFFLINE.</description></item><item><title>How to add an additional drive?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/how-to-add-an-additional-drive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/how-to-add-an-additional-drive/</guid><description>How to add an additional drive? # We recommend to run a new node, if you want to add an additional hard drive.
All nodes behind the same subnet /24 of a public IP are treated as a single node for ingress traffic and as separate ones for egress traffic (to the customers, repair and audit) - this is because we want to be decentralized as much as possible.</description></item><item><title>Where can I find the config.yaml?</title><link>/node/resources/faq/where-can-i-find-a-config-yaml/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/node/resources/faq/where-can-i-find-a-config-yaml/</guid><description>Where can I find the config.yaml? # Docker The config.yaml is created in your storage location when you did the initial setup of the storagenode.
For example, if your --mount option in your docker run command looks like --mount type=bind,source=/mnt/storj/storagenode,destination=/app/config, then the config.yaml will be in the /mnt/storj/storagenode location. Options and parameters specified in the docker run command have a precedence over options in the config.yaml - Only options not also specified in the docker run command will be taken from the config.</description></item></channel></rss>