<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>How To's on Storj Docs</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/</link><description>Recent content in How To's on Storj Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/dcs/how-tos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Container Registry - Docker</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/container-registry-docker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/container-registry-docker/</guid><description>Container Registry - Docker # Containers are wonderful: Containers provide a powerful way to package and deploy an application and make the runtime environment immutable and reproducible. But using containers also requires more infrastructure - distributing containers requires a docker registry, either a public one (like Dockerhub) or a private instance.
Under the hood, the container registry serves simple REST requests. As Storj DCS also can serve files via HTTP, it can be used as a container registry if the pieces are uploaded in the right order and mode.</description></item><item><title>Configure Tools for the Partner Program</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/configure-tools-for-the-partner-program/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/configure-tools-for-the-partner-program/</guid><description>Configure Tools for the Partner Program # Partner Program # The Storj Partner Ecosystem enables developers to build Storj DCS Connectors, which their customers can use to store data on Storj DSC.
The data itself is client-side encrypted, however we are able to measure the aggregate volume of storage and bandwidth usage. When a user of a Storj DCS Connector stores data in a bucket, we are able to give the partner attribution for the stored data and the used bandwidth for the Connector Integration, and provide programmatic revenue share.</description></item><item><title>Fastly Integration</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/fastly-integration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/fastly-integration/</guid><description>Fastly Integration # Prerequisites
Before you can connect your buckets to Fastly, you will first need a Fastly account. Once that is set up, follow the instructions below to configure a Fastly service with your buckets as an origin host.
Setting Up Fastly as an Edge Server # To make your buckets available through the Fastly edge cloud network, you will configure Storj as your Fastly service&amp;rsquo;s origin server.</description></item><item><title>Configure Filebase for easy upload</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/filebase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/filebase/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Backup With Duplicati</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/backup-with-duplicati/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/backup-with-duplicati/</guid><description>Backup With Duplicati # Overview # Duplicati is a backup tool. It can group, dedupe, and compress small files into bigger blocks. It is a great tool for reducing the costs of cold storage. It also supports versioning.
To restore a small file, Duplicati has to download the entire block it is contained in. Therefore, the best fit for Duplicati are the following two backup use cases: 1. when none of the files contained in the same block need to be ever restored again in the future.</description></item><item><title>NFT storage for OpenSea</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/nft-storage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/nft-storage/</guid><description>NFT storage for OpenSea # Storj DCS makes it easy for NFT (Non-Fungible Token) creators and developers to store their digital art, music, and videos on the decentralized cloud via Storj DCS.
Getting Started with NFT Storage on Storj DCS # In this tutorial, we’re going to cover three main steps:
Upload your Digital Asset to Storj DCS Create a public LinkShare link to your digital asset Register your NFT with the link to the asset Before we get started, here’s some background information on NFTs for context.</description></item><item><title>Backup With Restic</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/backup-with-restic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/backup-with-restic/</guid><description>Backup With Restic # Overview # Restic is a backup client written in Go language, it is highly secure and efficient. Each Restic backup is a snapshot of the server/files/directory, deduplicated from what was stored before. Any restore to a given backup will restore the server/files/directories to the exact state they were at that time.
This is a quick-start tutorial that covers Restic usage with Storj DCS.
In this guide, we will cover only some of the basic features of the tool.</description></item><item><title>FileZilla Native Integration</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/set-up-filezilla-for-decentralized-file-transfer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/set-up-filezilla-for-decentralized-file-transfer/</guid><description>FileZilla Native Integration # The native integration uses end-to-end encryption for your object data, including metadata and path data. This is the only integration available for the free version of Filezilla. If you wish to use the Hosted Gateway MT you will need the paid version of Filezilla. Background # The FileZilla Client is a fast and reliable cross-platform (Windows, Linux and Mac OS X) FTP, FTPS and SFTP client with lots of useful features and an intuitive graphical user interface.</description></item><item><title>Filezilla Pro Integration Guide</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/filezilla-pro-integration-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/filezilla-pro-integration-guide/</guid><description>Filezilla Pro Integration Guide # How to Integrate Filezilla Pro with Storj DCS to Easily Find, Transfer and Download All Of Your Files # At a quick glance, FileZilla provides a fast and reliable cross-platform (Windows, Linux and Mac OS X) FTP, FTPS and SFTP client that supports connections, file transfers and file structure browsing for many of today’s cloud data storage services, including Storj. This integration is beneficial for developers as it allows them to use the FileZilla Pro client to transfer files point-to-point using the decentralized cloud.</description></item><item><title>MongoDB Ops Manager Backup</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/mongodb-ops-manager-backup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/mongodb-ops-manager-backup/</guid><description>MongoDB Ops Manager Backup # Overview # MongoDB is a powerful, flexible, and scalable general purpose database. It combines the ability to scale out with features such as secondary indexes, range queries, sorting, aggregations, and geospatial indexes.
Ops Manager is a management platform that makes it easy to deploy, monitor, back up, and scale MongoDB on your own infrastructure.
MongoDB Enterprise supports a variety of cloud-native deployment options. This gives you and your apps access to locally deployed MongoDB clusters alongside direct access to MongoDB clusters running in the MongoDB Atlas cloud.</description></item><item><title>Store Tesla Sentry Mode &amp; Dashcam videos on Storj DCS</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/tesla-sentry-mode-teslausb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/tesla-sentry-mode-teslausb/</guid><description>Store Tesla Sentry Mode &amp;amp; Dashcam videos on Storj DCS # In this How To, we&amp;rsquo;ll demonstrate how to automatically transfer Tesla Sentry Mode and Dashcam video clips over WiFi to Storj DCS and make room for more videos the next day. We&amp;rsquo;ll use a Raspberry Pi (a small, low cost, low power computer) plugged into the USB port in the dashboard to store the video files. When the Tesla pulls into your garage at night, the Raspberry Pi will connect via WiFi and upload all the videos to Storj DCS, then clear off the drive for use the next day.</description></item><item><title>How to connect s3fs to Storj DCS</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/how-to-connect-s3fs-to-storj-dcs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/how-to-connect-s3fs-to-storj-dcs/</guid><description>How to connect s3fs to Storj DCS # Prerequisites # Before you get started, you need to have already made a satellite account, created an access grant and registered on the self-hosted S3-Compatible Gateway or generated credentials for Storj-hosted S3-Compatible Gateway.
Install s3fs # See https://github.com/s3fs-fuse/s3fs-fuse for installation instructions for your OS.
Configure s3fs to use Storj DCS S3 Gateway # You can use either Self-hosted S3 Compatible Gateway or Storj-hosted S3 Compatible Gateway.</description></item><item><title>How to set up video analytics and video management with Kerberos Vault</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/how-to-set-up-video-analytics-and-video-management-with-kerberos-vault/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/how-to-set-up-video-analytics-and-video-management-with-kerberos-vault/</guid><description>How to set up video analytics and video management with Kerberos Vault # Integration with Kerberos.io # The Kerberos.io project (not to be confused with the authentication protocol of the same name) offers an open-source platform for video analytics and monitoring. With a modular system design focused on minimal startup requirements and additional components available to add later, Kerberos.io is built to work for everything from small, personal systems to complex enterprise configurations.</description></item><item><title>How to Hod Rod File Transfer Performance on Storj DCS</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/how-to-hod-rod-file-transfer-performance-on-storj-dcs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/how-to-hod-rod-file-transfer-performance-on-storj-dcs/</guid><description>How to Hod Rod File Transfer Performance on Storj DCS # Many of the performance benefits of decentralized storage are achieved through distributed, redundant segmentation of files on the network. This redundancy and segmentation allows platforms like Storj to implement parallelism in the network for an even greater performance boost. In the context of file transfers, parallelism is the concept of uploading or downloading different pieces of a file simultaneously (in parallel).</description></item><item><title>Backups with HashBackup</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/backups-with-hashbackup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/backups-with-hashbackup/</guid><description>Backups with HashBackup # One of the most important things you can do to maintain the integrity and accessibility of your files is to routinely perform backups. Data backups are a familiar concept for many, allowing for efficient recovery from lost or damaged files.
The best way to benefit from data backups is to do them regularly. However, frequent backups can quickly start requiring significant storage space. This is especially true for long-term backups.</description></item><item><title>How to use Plex and Storj DCS as a private streaming service</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/how-to-use-plex-and-storj-dcs-as-a-private-streaming-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/how-to-use-plex-and-storj-dcs-as-a-private-streaming-service/</guid><description>How to use Plex and Storj DCS as a private streaming service # Video Storage # Managing a multimedia library can be tedious and time-consuming. Organizing your saved movies and TV shows into a streamable format requires effort to index, sort, and optimize the video files for playback. Fortunately, programs like Plex exist to make this easier. Plex is a media player platform that provides clients for desktop, mobile, and TV devices.</description></item><item><title>How to use Cyberduck and Storj DCS</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/how-to-use-cyberduck-and-storj-dcs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/how-to-use-cyberduck-and-storj-dcs/</guid><description>How to use Cyberduck and Storj DCS # Cyberduck is a free open-source libre server - a small server system which enables you to run your own internet services independently - cloud storage browser for macOS, Windows and Linux that supports FTP and SFTP, WebDAV, and cloud storage such as Storj DCS and other cloud storage providers.
Users can leverage the Cyberduck services via the user interface (GUI) or CLI (for Linux), including file transfer by drag and drop and notifications via Growl.</description></item><item><title>Storj IPFS Pinning Service (Beta)</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/storj-ipfs-pinning-service-beta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/storj-ipfs-pinning-service-beta/</guid><description>Storj IPFS Pinning Service (Beta) # Prerequisites # You should have received an email that you have been invited to the beta which will include credentials to access the service. If you have not signed up yet, you can Join the beta. The Storj IPFS Pinning service consists of an HTTP endpoint for uploading and pinning content, and an IPFS Gateway that serves the pinned content over IPFS and HTTP.</description></item><item><title>Simplify File Management with S3 Browser and Storj DCS</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/simplify-file-management-with-s3-browser-and-storj-dcs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/simplify-file-management-with-s3-browser-and-storj-dcs/</guid><description>Simplify File Management with S3 Browser and Storj DCS # S3 Browser is a Windows-based client that provides simple and reliable file management for AWS S3 storage and AWS S3 compatible storage such as Storj DCS. Via the intuitive web file management interface, users can store and retrieve files from their Storj DCS bucket anytime and anywhere.
While S3 Browser is free for personal use, users who wish to utilize the S3 Browser in commercial, business, government, or military institutions, or for any other profit activity, must purchase a pro license.</description></item><item><title>Kubernetes Backup via Velero</title><link>/dcs/how-tos/kubernetes-backup-via-velero/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dcs/how-tos/kubernetes-backup-via-velero/</guid><description>Kubernetes Backup via Velero # Background # This guide walks through the process of backing up a Kubernetes cluster using Restic with Velero. Velero is a command-line tool that backs up Kubernetes clusters and restores them in case of loss. Velero includes a command-line interface and server-side component that runs inside of your Kubernetes cluster.
Velero lets you:
Take backups of your cluster and restore them in case of loss.</description></item></channel></rss>